var questions = [
	//Category 1
	[
		"Plot",
		//100 points
		{
			question:"For how many years was Odysseus away?",
			answers:["One month", "One year", "Ten years", "Twenty years"],
			correctAnswer:3, //The correct answer is the fourth, but this is number 3 STARTING AT 0. I.e, first is "0", second is "1", third is "2", and fourth is "3"
			value:100,
			taken:false,
			correct:undefined,
		},
		//200 points
		{
			question:"What do the suitors do when hearing of Telemachus’ journey?",
			answers:["Try poisoning his drink", "Plan a naval ambush", "Compete more urgently for Penelope’s hand", "Flee the royal palace"],
			correctAnswer:1,
			value:200,
			taken:false,
			correct:undefined,
		},
		//300 points
		{
			question:" ... ",
			answers:[" ... ", " ... ", " ... ", " ... "],
			correctAnswer:0
		},
		//400 points
		{
			question:" ... ",
			answers:[" ... ", " ... ", " ... ", " ... "],
			correctAnswer:0
		},
		//500 points
		{
			question:" ... ",
			answers:[" ... ", " ... ", " ... ", " ... "],
			correctAnswer:0
		},
		//600 points
		{
			question:" ... ",
			answers:[" ... ", " ... ", " ... ", " ... "],
			correctAnswer:0
		},
	],
	//Category 2
	[
		"Characters",
		//100 points
		{
			question:"Which god assists Odysseus and later Telemachus many times throughout their journeys?",
			answers:["Athena", "Artemis", "Poseidon", "Zeus"],
			correctAnswer:0,
			value:100,
			taken:false,
			correct:undefined,
		},
		//200 points
		{
			question:"Under which disguise did Odysseus test Eumaeus?",
			answers:["A soldier", "A beggar", "Zeus", "He had no disguise"],
			correctAnswer:1,
			value:200,
			taken:false,
			correct:undefined,
		},
		//300 points
		{
			question:" ... ",
			answers:[" ... ", " ... ", " ... ", " ... "],
			correctAnswer:0
		},
		//400 points
		{
			question:" ... ",
			answers:[" ... ", " ... ", " ... ", " ... "],
			correctAnswer:0
		},
		//500 points
		{
			question:" ... ",
			answers:[" ... ", " ... ", " ... ", " ... "],
			correctAnswer:0
		},
		//600 points
		{
			question:" ... ",
			answers:[" ... ", " ... ", " ... ", " ... "],
			correctAnswer:0
		},
	],
	//More categories...
	//Category 3
	[
		"Category 3",
		//100 points
		{
			question:" ... ",
			answers:[" ... ", " ... ", " ... ", " ... "],
			correctAnswer:0,
			value:100,
			taken:false,
			correct:undefined,
		},
		//200 points
		{
			question:" ... ",
			answers:[" ... ", " ... ", " ... ", " ... "],
			correctAnswer:0,
			value:200,
			taken:false,
			correct:undefined,
		},
		//300 points
		{
			question:" ... ",
			answers:[" ... ", " ... ", " ... ", " ... "],
			correctAnswer:0
		},
		//400 points
		{
			question:" ... ",
			answers:[" ... ", " ... ", " ... ", " ... "],
			correctAnswer:0
		},
		//500 points
		{
			question:" ... ",
			answers:[" ... ", " ... ", " ... ", " ... "],
			correctAnswer:0
		},
		//600 points
		{
			question:" ... ",
			answers:[" ... ", " ... ", " ... ", " ... "],
			correctAnswer:0
		},
	],
	//Category 4
	[
		"Category 4",
		//100 points
		{
			question:" ... ",
			answers:[" ... ", " ... ", " ... ", " ... "],
			correctAnswer:0,
			value:100,
			taken:false,
			correct:undefined,
		},
		//200 points
		{
			question:" ... ",
			answers:[" ... ", " ... ", " ... ", " ... "],
			correctAnswer:0,
			value:200,
			taken:false,
			correct:undefined,
		},
		//300 points
		{
			question:" ... ",
			answers:[" ... ", " ... ", " ... ", " ... "],
			correctAnswer:0
		},
		//400 points
		{
			question:" ... ",
			answers:[" ... ", " ... ", " ... ", " ... "],
			correctAnswer:0
		},
		//500 points
		{
			question:" ... ",
			answers:[" ... ", " ... ", " ... ", " ... "],
			correctAnswer:0
		},
		//600 points
		{
			question:" ... ",
			answers:[" ... ", " ... ", " ... ", " ... "],
			correctAnswer:0
		},
	],
];